[
    {
        "question": "ناروتو",
        "response": "ناروتو"
    },
    {
        "question": "كونان",
        "response": "كونان"
    },
    {
        "question": "اكاي",
        "response": "اكاي"
    },
    {
        "question": "انجيلو",
        "response": "انجيلو"
    },
    {
        "question": "ميكو",
        "response": "ميكو"
    },
    {
        "question": "مادارا",
        "response": "مادارا"
    },
    {
        "question": "نامي",
        "response": "نامي"
    },
    {
        "question": "روبين",
        "response": "روبين"
    },
    {
        "question": "لوفي",
        "response": "لوفي"
    },
    {
        "question": "لايت",
        "response": "لايت"
    },
    {
        "question": "ال",
        "response": "ال"
    },
    {
        "question": "آي",
        "response": "آي"
    },
    {
        "question": "روبي",
        "response": "روبي"
    },
    {
        "question": "تانجيرو",
        "response": "تانجيرو"
    },
    {
        "question": "نيزوكو",
        "response": "نيزوكو"
    },
    {
        "question": "زينيتسو",
        "response": "زينيتسو"
    },
    {
        "question": "كانيكي",
        "response": "كانيكي"
    },
    {
        "question": "سيرينا",
        "response": "سيرينا"
    },
    {
        "question": "نيشيميا",
        "response": "نيشيميا"
    },
    {
        "question": "ريكي",
        "response": "ريكي"
    },
    {
        "question": "ميرو",
        "response": "ميرو"
    },
    {
        "question": "زورو",
        "response": "زورو"
    },
    {
        "question": "ميراجين",
        "response": "ميراجين"
    },
    {
        "question": "باغي",
        "response": "باغي"
    },
    {
        "question": "ريكا",
        "response": "ريكا"
    },
    {
        "question": "سانجي",
        "response": "سانجي"
    },
    {
        "question": "اوتا",
        "response": "اوتا"
    },
    {
        "question": "دازاي",
        "response": "دازاي"
    },
    {
        "question": "فيودور",
        "response": "فيودور"
    },
    {
        "question": "يوتا",
        "response": "يوتا"
    },
    {
        "question": "اثي",
        "response": "اثي"
    },
    {
        "question": "لولوش",
        "response": "لولوش"
    },
    {
        "question": "ايري",
        "response": "ايري"
    },
    {
        "question": "شوكو",
        "response": "شوكو"
    },
    {
        "question": "يوميكو",
        "response": "يوميكو"
    },
    {
        "question": "جيرايا",
        "response": "جيرايا"
    },
    {
        "question": "جان",
        "response": "جان"
    },
    {
        "question": "سيبر",
        "response": "سيبر"
    },
    {
        "question": "جيمي",
        "response": "جيمي"
    },
    {
        "question": "جاكس",
        "response": "جاكس"
    },
    {
        "question": "هيماواري",
        "response": "هيماواري"
    },
    {
        "question": "هومورا",
        "response": "هومورا"
    },
    {
        "question": "هيكاري",
        "response": "هيكاري"
    },
    {
        "question": "هيستوريا",
        "response": "هيستوريا"
    },
    {
        "question": "هيرا",
        "response": "هيرا"
    },
    {
        "question": "هيرو",
        "response": "هيرو"
    },
    {
        "question": "هوليا",
        "response": "هوليا"
    },
    {
        "question": "هانكوك",
        "response": "هانكوك"
    },
    {
        "question": "هوشينو",
        "response": "هوشينو"
    },
    {
        "question": "هوري",
        "response": "هوري"
    },
    {
        "question": "هاتوري",
        "response": "هاتوري"
    },
    {
        "question": "هانا",
        "response": "هانا"
    },
    {
        "question": "هاناكو",
        "response": "هاناكو"
    },
    {
        "question": "هانجي",
        "response": "هانجي"
    },
    {
        "question": "هاهوري",
        "response": "هاهوري"
    },
    {
        "question": "هوكس",
        "response": "هوكس"
    },
    {
        "question": "تيناري",
        "response": "تيناري"
    },
    {
        "question": "هوني",
        "response": "هوني"
    },
    {
        "question": "هياتو",
        "response": "هياتو"
    },
    {
        "question": "هيتاري",
        "response": "هيتاري"
    },
    {
        "question": "هيسوكا",
        "response": "هيسوكا"
    },
    {
        "question": "هيراجي",
        "response": "هيراجي"
    },
    {
        "question": "هيلجا",
        "response": "هيلجا"
    },
    {
        "question": "هيلوكيتي",
        "response": "هيلوكيتي"
    },
    {
        "question": "هيناتسوري",
        "response": "هيناتسوري"
    },
    {
        "question": "غورين",
        "response": "غورين"
    },
    {
        "question": "ناهيدا",
        "response": "ناهيدا"
    },
    {
        "question": "زونجلي",
        "response": "زونجلي"
    },
    {
        "question": "غيلبرت",
        "response": "غيلبرت"
    },
    {
        "question": "غينيا",
        "response": "غينيا"
    },
    {
        "question": "غان",
        "response": "غان"
    },
    {
        "question": "فاسكو",
        "response": "فاسكو"
    },
    {
        "question": "فاي",
        "response": "فاي"
    },
    {
        "question": "فايوليت",
        "response": "فايوليت"
    },
    {
        "question": "فيو",
        "response": "فيو"
    },
    {
        "question": "فوشيا",
        "response": "فوشيا"
    },
    {
        "question": "فوكو",
        "response": "فوكو"
    },
    {
        "question": "فيرموث",
        "response": "فيرموث"
    },
    {
        "question": "فيغو",
        "response": "فيغو"
    },
    {
        "question": "فيولا",
        "response": "فيولا"
    },
    {
        "question": "فيونا",
        "response": "فيونا"
    },
    {
        "question": "قارا",
        "response": "قارا"
    },
    {
        "question": "ثورفين",
        "response": "ثورفين"
    },
    {
        "question": "صوفي",
        "response": "صوفي"
    },
    {
        "question": "صوفيا",
        "response": "صوفيا"
    },
    {
        "question": "طوكيو",
        "response": "طوكيو"
    },
    {
        "question": "كرولو",
        "response": "كرولو"
    },
    {
        "question": "كازوها",
        "response": "كازوها"
    },
    {
        "question": "كوباياشي",
        "response": "كوباياشي"
    },
    {
        "question": "كابتشينو",
        "response": "كابتشينو"
    },
    {
        "question": "كاتسومي",
        "response": "كاتسومي"
    },
    {
        "question": "كابورامارو",
        "response": "كابورامارو"
    },
    {
        "question": "كاتسومي",
        "response": "كاتسومي"
    },
    {
        "question": "كاتشان",
        "response": "كاتشان"
    },
    {        
        "question": "كاجومي",
        "response": "كاجومي"
    },
    {
        "question": "كازي",
        "response": "كازي"
    },
    {
        "question": "كاميشيرو",
        "response": "كاميشيرو"
    },
    {
        "question": "كاناو",
        "response": "كاناو"
    },
    {
        "question": "كيرا",
        "response": "كيرا"
    },
    {
        "question": "كانا",
        "response": "كانا"
    },
    {
        "question": "كايلا",
        "response": "كايلا"
    },
    {
        "question": "كايينا",
        "response": "كايينا"
    },
    {
        "question": "كراول",
        "response": "كراول"
    },
    {
        "question": "كريستا",
        "response": "كريستا"
    },
    {
        "question": "كلوي",
        "response": "كلوي"
    },
    {
        "question": "كوزاكورا",
        "response": "كوزاكورا"
    },
    {
        "question": "كوزيت",
        "response": "كوزيت"
    },
    {
        "question": "كوشينا",
        "response": "كوشينا"
    },
    {
        "question": "كيري",
        "response": "كيري"
    },
    {
        "question": "استنر",
        "response": "استنر"
    },
    {
        "question": "كيوكا",
        "response": "كيوكا"
    },
    {
        "question": "كيوكاي",
        "response": "كيوكاي"
    },
    {
        "question": "كان",
        "response": "كان"
    },
    {
        "question": "كايتو كيد",
        "response": "كايتو كيد"
    },
    {
        "question": "اينوسكي",
        "response": "اينوسكي"
    },
    {
        "question": "غيو",
        "response": "غيو"
    },
    {
        "question": "ميتسوري",
        "response": "ميتسوري"
    },
    {
        "question": "شينوبو",
        "response": "شينوبو"
    },
    {
        "question": "توميوكا",
        "response": "توميوكا"
    },
    {


        "question": "ارثر",
        "response": "ارثر"
    },
    {

        "question": "جين وو",
        "response": "جين وو"
    },
    {


        "question": "موزان",
        "response": "موزان"
    },
    {


        "question": "غيومي",
        "response": "غيومي"
    },
    {


        "question": "اكازا",
        "response": "اكازا"
    },
    {


        "question": "دوما",
        "response": "دوما"
    },
    {
      
        "question": "كوكوشيبو",
        "response": "كوكوشيبو"
    },
    {
      
        "question": "ريو",
        "response": "ريو"
    },
    {


        "question": "شارلوك",
        "response": "شارلوك"
    },
    {
      
        "question": "ويليام",
        "response": "ويليام"
    },
    {


        "question": "شيرلوك",
        "response": "شيرلوك"
    },
    {


        "question": "يويتشي",
        "response": "يويتشي"
    },
    {


        "question": "يوو",
        "response": "يوو"
    },
    {


        "question": "توموري",
        "response": "توموري"
    },
    {


        "question": "ايانوكوجي",
        "response": "ايانوكوجي"
    },
    {
      
        "question": "كيوتاكا",
        "response": "كيوتاكا"
    },
    {


        "question": "ريوك",
        "response": "ريوك"
    },
    {


        "question": "سوزوني",
        "response": "سوزوني"
    },
    {


        "question": "كيريتو",
        "response": "كيريتو"
    },
    {


        "question": "اسونا",
        "response": "اسونا"
    },
    {


        "question": "فاليريا",
        "response": "فاليريا"
    },
    {


        "question": "كيارو",
        "response": "كيارو"
    },
    {


        "question": "هيناتا",
        "response": "هيناتا"
    },
    {


        "question": "ايومي",
        "response": "ايومي"
    },
    {


        "question": "ابيل",
        "response": "ابيل"
    },
    {


        "question": "استا",
        "response": "استا"
    },
    {


        "question": "يونو",
        "response": "يونو"
    },
    {


        "question": "اينوسينت زيرو",
        "response": "اينوسينت زيرو"
    },
    {


        "question": "بامي",
        "response": "يامي"
    },
    {


        "question": "يوليوس",
        "response": "يوليوس"
    },
    {


        "question": "ماش",
        "response": "ماش"
    },
    {


        "question": "ايرين",
        "response": "ايرين"
    },
    {


        "question": "ليفاي",
        "response": "ليفاي"
    },
    {


        "question": "هبنا",
        "response": "هينا"
    },
    {


        "question": "ايروين",
        "response": "ايروين"
    },
    {


        "question": "ميكاسا",
        "response": "ميكاسا"
    },
    {


        "question": "هو تاو",
        "response": "هو تاو"
    },
    {
      
        "question": "نيوفيليت",
        "response": "نيوفيليت"
    },
    {
      
        "question": "ارليكينو",
        "response": "ارليكينو"
    },
    {
      
        "question": "ايولا",
        "response": "ايولا"
    },
    {


        "question": "نوبارا",
        "response": "نوبارا"
    },
    {


        "question": "غوجو",
        "response": "غوجو"
    },
    {


        "question": "الهيثم",
        "response": "الهيثم"
    },
    {


        "question": "ايتادوري",
        "response": "ايتادوري"
    },
    {


        "question": "اياكا",
        "response": "اياكا"
    },
    {


        "question": "ساينو",
        "response": "ساينو"
    },
    {


        "question": "بال",
        "response": "بال"
    },
    {


        "question": "جين",
        "response": "جين"
    },
    {


        "question": "شوتو",
        "response": "شوتو"
    },
    {


        "question": "نافيا",
        "response": "نافيا"
    },
    {


        "question": "شادو",
        "response": "شادو"
    },
    {


        "question": "بيو وول",
        "response": "بيو وول"
    },
    {


        "question": "اياتو",
        "response": "اياتو"
    },
    {


        "question": "روديوس",
        "response": "روديوس"
    },
    {
       "question": "مارس",
       "response": "مارس"
}
]
